<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<project>
	<PreviewIconFile>preview_icon.png</PreviewIconFile>
	<ItemDescriptionShort>Gyll’s Vanilla: Flagellant reworks the Flagellant into a versatile healer and bleed-based damage dealer, with fewer special mechanics and less reliance on situational self-heal skills.</ItemDescriptionShort>
	<ModDataPath>C:/DarkestDungeon/mods/gylls_vanilla_flagellant/</ModDataPath>
	<Title>Gyll&apos;s Vanilla: Flagellant</Title>
	<Language>english</Language>
	<UpdateDetails/>
	<Visibility>public</Visibility>
	<UploadMode>copy_and_upload</UploadMode>
	<VersionMajor>0</VersionMajor>
	<VersionMinor>0</VersionMinor>
	<TargetBuild>21142</TargetBuild>
	<Tags>
		<Tags>Class Tweaks</Tags>
	</Tags>
	<ItemDescription>
[b]Gyll’s Vanilla: Flagellant[/b] reworks the Flagellant into a versatile healer and bleed-based damage dealer, with fewer special mechanics and less reliance on situational self-heal skills.

[h1]Design Goals for the Flagellant[/h1]
- Drastically tone down his self heal skills
- Make him feel more like a normal hero
- Allow him to be a viable main healer
- Give him a viable backline build

[h1]Changelog[/h1]
[url=https://dd-tooltips.com/flagellant]Click to view the changelog, including tooltips and design notes[/url]

[h1]About Gyll’s Vanilla[/h1]
[b]Gyll’s Vanilla[/b] is a collection of mods for Darkest Dungeon, each of which redesigns a single aspect of the game. These mods are balanced against the vanilla base game and designed for maximum compatibility, creating a solid foundation for your modded campaigns.
[url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1407664617]Click to view the full collection[/url]

[h1]Disclaimer[/h1]
[i]Gyll’s Vanilla: Flagellant is not an official Red Hook Studios product or product modification, and Red Hook Studios Inc. is not responsible in any way for changes or damages that may result from using the mod. Furthermore, “Darkest Dungeon” and the Darkest Dungeon logo are trademarks of Red Hook Studios Inc. All content in the game is Copyright Red Hook Studios Inc. All rights reserved.[/i]
	</ItemDescription>
	<PublishedFileId>1408032394</PublishedFileId>
</project>

